What do you fear?
Phobias is a horror, thriller film directed by Camilla Belle.
Five dangerous patients, suffering from extreme phobias at a government testing facility, are put to the
ultimate test under the supervision of a crazed doctor and his quest to weaponize fear.
Lia, played by Alexis Knapp.
Emma, played by Lauren Miller Rogen.
Natalie, played by Monique Coleman.
Alma, played by Martina García.
Sami, played by Hana Mae Lee.
Phobias is a 2021 American horror thriller film written by Camilla Belle, Broderick Engelhard, Maritte Lee Go, Joe Sill, Jess Varley and Chris von Hoffmann, directed by Camilla Belle,
Maritte Lee Go, Joe Sill, Jess Varley and Chris von Hoffman and starring Leonardo Nam, Alexis Knapp, Hana Mae Lee, Lauren Miller Rogen, Charlotte McKinney and Martina García.
The tone is dark and intense.